Now that our app is showing real data, we should take
a screenshot of our app, so we can remember what it was
like when we made it this far. I personally like doing this
throughout the process of building an app, because then I can look
back, and see how it evolved. I'm going to show you one
way that you can take a screenshot of your device. Open up
Android Device Monitor and then click on the device here. Then, click
on this camera icon, to do a screen capture. When it pops
up, you can hit Save, and then you're done.
On certain physical devices, there are actually hardware keys that
allow you to grab a screenshot. For example, on the
Nexus 5, you can long press on the volume down
and the power key, at the same time. That takes
a screenshot. It gets saved to the Photos app and
then you can share it out to anyone you want.
You can show them what an awesome app you're building.